http://www.jaytee.com/privacy/

SGE Syringes
Gas Tight (10µL – 100mL)
MicroVolume (0.5µL – 500µL)
HPLC Flowmeter
Lab Gas Generators (CLAIND)
0
No products in the cart.
SGE Syringes
Gas Tight (10µL – 100mL)
MicroVolume (0.5µL – 500µL)
HPLC Flowmeter
Lab Gas Generators (CLAIND)
How we use your information
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Jaytee Biosciences ltd (Jaytee) collects personal information. It applies to information we collect about:
visitors to our websites;
complainants and other individuals in relation to a data protection or freedom of information complaint or enquiry;
people who use our services, eg who subscribe to our newsletter;
people who notify under the General Data Protection Regulations;
job applicants and our current and former employees
Visitors to our websites
When someone visits www.jaytee.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. If we do want to collect personally identifiable information through our website, we will be up front about this. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to do with it.
Use of cookies by Jaytee
There is a technology called “cookies” which can be used to provide You with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to Your browser, which may then be stored on Your computer system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program. We can only access the information from a cookie sent by the web site. We cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. Additionally, We cannot learn Your email address or any other information about You through the use of a cookie. The only way We would learn such information is if You specifically submit that information to Us.
Search engine
No user-specific data is collected by either Jaytee or any third party.
E-newsletter
We use a third party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our e-newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies including clear gifs to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. When you opt in to receive marketing information from us (via our contact form or newsletter sign-up form), the MailChimp platform allows you to edit your profile, or unsubscribe from the service. Each communication that we send via MailChimp includes links to allow you to access this functionality.
For more information, please see MailChimp’s privacy policy.
People who email us
We monitor any emails sent to us, including file attachments, for viruses or malicious software. Please be aware that you have a responsibility to ensure that any email you send is within the bounds of the law.
Job applicants, current and former Jaytee employees
Jaytee is the data controller for the information you provide during the process application process. If you have any queries about the process or how we handle your information please contact us at jobs@jaytee.com.
What will we do with the information you provide to us?
All of the information you provide during the process will only be used for the purpose of progressing your application, or to fulfil legal or regulatory requirements if necessary.
We will not share any of the information you provide during the recruitment process with any third parties for marketing purposes or store any of your information outside of the European Economic Area. The information you provide will be held securely by us and/or our data processors whether the information is in electronic or physical format.
We will use the contact details you provide to us to contact you to progress your application. We will use the other information you provide to assess your suitability for the role you have applied for.
What information do we ask for, and why?
We do not collect more information than we need to fulfil our stated purposes. During the application process we will ask if we can retain your information for future vacancies, should you be unsuccessful with this application. The information we ask for is used to assess your suitability for employment. You don’t have to provide what we ask for but it might affect your application if you don’t.
Conditional offer
If you are successful we will make a conditional offer of employment and ask you for information so that we can carry out pre-employment checks. You must successfully complete pre-employment checks to progress to a final offer. We are required to confirm the identity of our staff, their right to work in the United Kingdom and seek assurance as to their trustworthiness, integrity and reliability.
You will therefore be required to provide:
Proof of your identity – you will be asked to attend our office with original documents, we will take copies.
Proof of your qualifications – you will be asked to attend our office with original documents, we will take copies.
You may be asked to complete a criminal records declaration to declare any unspent convictions.
We may provide your email address to the Government Recruitment Service who will contact you to complete an application for a Basic Criminal Record check via the Disclosure and Barring Service, or Access NI, which will verify your declaration of unspent convictions.
We will contact your referees, using the details you provide in your application, directly to obtain references
If we make a final offer, we will also ask you for the following:
Bank details – to process salary payments
Emergency contact details – so we know who to contact in case you have an emergency at work
ATLAS
If you accept a final offer from us, some of your personnel records will be held on ATLAS which is an internally used HR records system.
How long is the information retained for?
If you are successful, the information you provide during the application process will be retained by us as part of your employee file for the duration of your employment plus 6 years following the end of your employment. This includes your criminal records declaration, fitness to work, records of any security checks and references.
If you are unsuccessful at any stage of the process, the information you have provided until that point will be retained for 6 months from the closure of the campaign. (unless you have given us permission to retain the information for consideration to future vacancies).
Information generated throughout the assessment process, for example interview notes, is retained by us for 6 months following the closure of the campaign.
How we make decisions about recruitment
Final recruitment decisions are made by hiring managers and members of our recruitment team. All of the information gathered during the application process is taken into account.
You are able to ask about decisions made about your application by speaking to your contact within our recruitment team or by emailing jobs@jaytee.com.
Your rights
Under the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) 2018, you have rights as an individual which you can exercise in relation to the information we hold about you.
Complaints or queries
Jaytee tries to meet the highest standards when collecting and using personal information. For this reason, we take any complaints we receive about this very seriously. We encourage people to bring it to our attention if they think that our collection or use of information is unfair, misleading or inappropriate. We would also welcome any suggestions for improving our procedures.
This privacy notice was drafted with brevity and clarity in mind. It does not provide exhaustive detail of all aspects of Jaytee’s collection and use of personal information. However, we are happy to provide any additional information or explanation needed. Any requests for this should be sent to the address below.
If you want to make a complaint about the way we have processed your personal information, you can contact us at – info@jaytee.com.
Access to personal information
Jaytee tries to be as open as it can be in terms of giving people access to their personal information. Individuals can find out if we hold any personal information by making a ‘subject access request’ under the Data Protection Act 1998. If we do hold information about you we will:
give you a description of it;
tell you why we are holding it;
tell you who it could be disclosed to; and
let you have a copy of the information in an intelligible form.
To make a request to Jaytee for any personal information we may hold, you need to put the request in writing addressing it to “Personal Information Request, Jaytee Biosciences, CT6 6GZ, UK”.
If you agree, we will try to deal with your request informally, for example by providing you with the specific information you need over the telephone.
If we do hold information about you, you can ask us to correct any mistakes by, once again, contacting the address above.
Links to other websites
This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.
Changes to this privacy notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This privacy notice was last updated on 18th May 2018.
How to contact us
If you want to request information about our privacy policy you can jaytee.com/contact or write to:
How can we help you?
Your Name (required)
Your Email (required)
Your Message
Please leave this field empty.What is 7 divided by 2 (required)
I wish to be contacted by Jaytee Biosciences Ltd regarding this enquiry.
I am happy to be contacted in future by Jaytee Biosciences Ltd in related matters.
This site uses cookiesOkay, thanksFind out more
Receive our regular newsletter:×
